Sorry, Jun.
I promised Misuzu and Carol
I'd walk home with them today.
It's cool. Don't worry about it.
You're taking this awfully well, Jun-kun.
Not going to get all dejected this time?
I'll never get dejected over not
going home together anymore.
I don't want to be the kind
of guy who ties Tomo down.
Jun...
What the... S-Stop!
Lately... Actually, for a while now...
I think it started when he started
to see me as a girl, to be honest...
But Jun's been so relaxed,
it's actually kinda pissing me off.
I get it.
I get it, too.
It's like I'm the only one freaking out,
and it makes me feel like I've lost.
I don't think it's an issue
of winning or losing,
but I get that you want to
see him acting flustered.
Then... why not kiss him?
Huh?! K-Kiss him?! Are you...
If it was that easy, I wouldn't
be suffering like this!
You could try watching
a kissing scene together.
I bet that would make him think about it.
D-Does it really work like that?
It'll be Christmas soon.
Why don't you go see this together?
When I throw a jab or a straight,
it always lands
But when I'm aiming for your heart,
I miss every time
Parallel, zigzagging, awkward, incoherent
When you look my way and move closer to me
I know it doesn't mean the same thing for you
But I wish we could stay like this forever
My changing feelings are driving me crazy
The moment you turn to face me,
take that! Telepathy
If only we could feel the same thing
I want to kick this pesky subtlety away
I want to know everything,
I want to know everything
I can't fool you forever
I can't keep this hidden
I want to shout out my secret, AHHH
Take that! Telepathy
Te-te-te-telepathy
Telepathy
To Stay by Your Side...
"To Stay by Your Side..."
Jun!
Did you wait long?
You look kinda grown-up today.
You think so?
What about me? Well? Well?
Hey, c'mon! Look at me!
Tomo...
You look... cute today. Pretty, in fact.
There's just something special
about this look. I really like it.
Sorry... I'm not used to this kind
of thing, so I can't say it well...
Y-Yeah...
Damn him!
We're gonna see this today!
What?!
This Love Is the Real Deal!! A Story of Pure Love
Are you actually serious?
C'mon, Jun. We're not little kids anymore.
You can't panic over a little kiss.
Wh-When did you turn into
that kind of adult?!
Heh!
This Love Is the Real Deal!! A Story of Pure Love
Staring at this thing for
a whole week paid off!
Wait, Haruko!
We should stop seeing each other.
But why?!
You're someone I must never love!
Forgive me, Keita-kun.
When it gets to the kissing scene,
put your hand on top of his.
The effect will be immediate.
All right! Bring it on, kissing scene!
Wait, what?!
We can't! Not here!
I can't hold back anymore!
I love you, Haruko.
Okay. Come to me, Keita-kun.
Haruko... Haruko!
Did Misuzu go see this movie by herself?!
This is way beyond just a kiss!
If I put my hand on his now,
it'll look like I'm asking for this!
Damn! He's really taking this in!
Keita-kun...
Haruko...
The movie was... p-pretty interesting, huh?
Yeah. I guess it pays to go
into things with an open mind.
You were looking really focused.
Are you into that kinda thing?
Does he like pervy stuff that much?!
I actually couldn't get into love
and romance stories before.
I always thought I was the kind of
guy who couldn't relate to all that.
But now... I don't know why...
Because I fell in love with you, maybe?
I'm total scum!
Oh, yeah.
Here. It's your Christmas present.
Thanks...
Go on. Open it.
Wh-What do you think?
This kind of thing really
doesn't suit me, huh?
I'm so glad I bought those.
Say something!
Actually, I have something for you, too.
Here you go.
No way... Is this a handmade muffler?!
I heard it was a classic gift choice,
so I gave it a shot,
but it didn't come out well
enough to actually wear around.
I bet you feel pretty
awkward just accepting it.
Don't just put it on right away!
The truth is, I don't have any
complaints about the way Jun is now.
I know he's acting calmer
because I'm important to him.
It's just... Somehow, I've gotten greedy.
I want to shock him more!
I want to make him like me more!
It's getting dark. Ready to head home?
I'll go... to your house.
Huh?!
But it's already night—
So your mom's out again today, huh?
I think she'll be back by nightfall, though.
Oh.
I know!
Wanna play some games?
No, I'm good.
Okay.
Chill out, me!
I've been alone with Tomo in my
own room tons of times before!
Hey...
Can I...
sit next to you?
I knew I wasn't cut out for bargaining!
I came here today... to kiss you!
Kiss me?!
T-To kiss me?! Where did that even...
You don't want to?
No, it's not that I don't want to...
I guess...
I don't have any feminine
appeal after all, huh?
Tomo!
Huh?! Jun?!
Is it gonna happen?!
Are we...
Are we about to do that?!
He's making a fist?!
Is that a thing, too?!
What?!
What the hell are you doing?! Are you okay?!
Tomo...
You have so much appeal!
The desire to kiss you... a-and touch you...
is constantly on my mind!
Huh?!
But I don't think it's right to just
do those things without any thought!
I want them to be special.
Jun...
So I can't do that now.
I haven't even asked you
to be my girlfriend yet.
You're right. We're not even going out yet.
Wait, we weren't even going out yet?!
Actually, after I told you
how I felt about you,
I went to talk to your parents.
Akemi-san gave our
relationship her blessing,
but your dad...
If you want to date Tomo,
you have to defeat me first!
That's what he said.
Dad, you stupid piece of shit!
How could you tell him he can't date
Tomo unless he beats you? Poor Jun-bo.
Yeah.
So? Why are you all depressed now?
Tomo is...
She's really my daughter, huh?
You're asking that after all this time?
You won't find a cuter
daughter than her anywhere.
Damn you, old man!
Tomo?
You know what this is about, don't you?
Mm...
Why'd you tell him he can't
date me unless he defeats you?
What were you thinking when
you said that to Jun?!
M-Mm...
Quit your stupid grunting
and answer me, asshole!
M-Mm...
Damn it! You're gonna keep
me in the dark, then?
Forget it!
Tomo?
Dad...
I hate you!
She hates me?!
Happy New Year, Misuzu-chan.
Happy New Year.
You still can't get in touch with Tomo-chan?
No.
She won't answer her phone,
and my messages aren't even
being marked as read.
I wanted to do our first shrine
visit of the year with her.
You haven't heard anything from
her since Christmas, right?
That's right.
It's Jun-kun, isn't it?
Yes. It has to be him.
Sorry to tell you after you
took the time to come over,
Aizawa
but she's still saying she
doesn't want to see anyone.
I see.
H-Hey, I know! Why don't you
try fighting Goro right now?
He's been off his game.
He might be easier to beat than you think.
No, I'm not in the mood to
fight right now, either.
N-No, huh?
Back at School
Just wait a minute!
Shut up!
I said wait, Tomo!
Do you know why I'm pissed off?
Because I didn't tell
you what your dad said?
Bingo. Why didn't you tell me?
Because...
You could have just told me
that you'd go kick my dad's ass,
so I could just take it easy and wait!
Then I would've...
I can't just ask you to wait for me!
I don't... have to wait?
Yeah. Since it's come to this,
I intend to face it with all I've got.
But I know it's not gonna be
that easy to beat your dad.
Defeating him was already my life's goal.
So if I go through my whole
life never able to beat him,
I'll just...
Get...
Get real!
As long as Jun's like that, he'll never win,
no matter how capable he is!
Long time no see.
How have you been, Tomo-chan?
You completely ignored us
all through winter break,
so I guess it's been two weeks?
Do you remember when we said
we'd all go skiing together?
Um... I'm... really sorry...
So that's what happened.
Well? Do you think he can win?
H-He can!
Maybe not right away, but...
If he takes his training seriously,
maybe in a few months...
No, maybe a few years...
That's too long.
So what are you going to do?
What do you want me to say?
There's nothing I can do.
And that's okay with you?
If you want to take the heroine's
stance of silently observing
a battle between two men, that's fine.
But is that what you want?
Tomo!
Wh-What?!
I'm gonna challenge your dad today.
Kashima Daimyojin
Damn.
Jun-bo! What the hell are you thinking?!
You said you'd accept my challenge
at any time, didn't you?
So you will accept it, right?
Very well, then.
I thought if I said that, you'd
give up on Tomo and run away.
I realize I'm at a huge disadvantage.
So I'll do whatever I have to do to defeat you.
And on that note...
I've called in some support.
H-How dare you?!
Br-Br-Bringing Akemi here is playing dirty!
Jun's challenging my dad right now.
Should I really just stay here?
Aizawa-san... If something's bothering you,
you can talk to me...
Huh?
I see. So he really went to
challenge Goro-san, huh?
Jun-kun's amazing.
You said it.
Wait, Senpai, you knew Jun was
going to challenge my dad?
Yeah, actually, he seemed stressed
about something over winter break,
so I asked what was up, and...
I know I don't have much chance of winning,
but I'm pretty sure this is
a battle I have to fight.
So as long as Tomo doesn't abandon me, I...
"I can't give up," he said.
Since he's such a sincere guy, I figured he
was fighting 'cause he thought he had to...
I think you should cheer Jun-kun on.
I'm sure you know better than anyone...
what would help him the most.
Sorry, Senpai!
I gotta leave early today!
Was that...
Yeah, that wind pressure
was definitely Tomo.
Looks like she's over it. That's great.
You're right. She must have had an epiphany.
Why don't you just give up already?
You can't defeat me as you are now.
Not... Not yet!
Hey, you okay? You're really wrecked.
This is nothi—
Wait, Tomo?!
Wh-Why are you here?!
Well, I was thinking about it.
You wanna go out with me, right?
Huh?
I wanna go out with you, too!
And the only one in the way of that...
is my old man!
So it's fine if I defeat you instead, right?
What kind of logic is that?!
This is between me and your dad!
I know, I know!
I'm not trying to show up in the
middle of your fight and butt in.
But if you go down and can't get
back up, then it's my turn.
And I'll beat him, so you can lose
without worrying about anything.
Those eyes... She's serious.
Oh, really?
Well, now you've done it.
That's a hell of a lot of pressure!
Yo, Jun. I was watching for
a bit, and I think Dad...
Yeah, I know.
I'd like one more round, please.
Hmph. You never learn.
Something's different about him today.
He's taking some wide swings
that leave him open.
If he's doing that on purpose,
then what he's testing is...
There it is! A wide right!
As often as he's doing it,
it's gotta be intentional.
And if there's an opening,
I just have to take it!
It's as simple as that...
to say, at least!
Kashima Daimyojin
I can't beat him with hit-and-away
strikes that have no momentum.
I have to step right into his reach,
without thinking about consequences,
and deal a counter that uses
his own strength against him.
That's probably what it's
gonna take to beat him.
That's a real challenge for me.
But it's a hurdle Tomo
could overcome easily.
That's probably the point of this test.
Every day, somewhere in this world,
someone is unfairly getting hurt.
What if that happened
to someone close to me?
Tomo would act faster than anyone.
If I hesitate for a second,
she'll be beyond my reach,
and I'll end up leaving her alone.
I get it, old man.
That's why you're so worried
about her, isn't it?
I'm sorry the man next to
her is someone like me.
Here I come!
Come.
I'm not like Tomo.
I can't put my life on the
line for a total stranger.
The only one I could hope to do that for...
is the girl I love!
Go, Jun!
Jun... wo—
Not enough!
What?!
Oh, enough already!
Huh?
It's true.
For just a moment, my fingers
did touch the floor.
You win, Junichiro.
I... I actually beat—
Yes!
You won! You beat him!
C'mon, Tomo, that hurts!
Well done.
You actually did it!
I give! I give!
So you beat Dad, right?
Yeah.
Which means... it's okay now, right?
Y'know, to go out with m—
Wait!
I love you, Tomo! Please go out with me!
Huh?
What?!
I was about to say that!
Why'd you interrupt?!
Why'd you have to say it?!
It's the guy's job to say that, isn't it?
There's no law saying it has to be!
If you're gonna do that, then I'm gonna...
Wh-What did you just...
You were amazing.
Huh?
When you beat my dad, you looked amazing.
Watching you made my heart race.
But...
You'd better be ready!
From now on, I'm gonna be making
your heart race a lot more!
I guess it's on, then.
Yeah!
You'll never beat me!
(This suspicious behavior is...)
Hey, you know, I'm all mixed up
It's too complicated, I'm freaking out
I want to look cute to you
(crazy, crazy, drive me crazy, and that's…)
So I'm plotting, bargaining,
sly, and stubborn
Dizzying love
Just tell him to look at you
And watch him stiffen up even more,
because you're both so awkward
What? Even if we're alike in that way
It doesn't make me happy, 'cause it
means our love is going nowhere
Cloudy heart, swirling emotions—
I sense rain coming
So I partly open my umbrella,
then sneakily scoot closer to you
Please notice the curl of my
eyelashes as I keep blinking
And don't say I'm acting weird
One year ago, in spring, I confessed my love.
All this plotting and bargaining
is my sly plan to look cute to you
Without the support of everyone around me,
this love wouldn't have come to be.
Try to solve the riddle of
this soft, dizzying love
(Buzzing, fidgeting)
I, Aizawa Tomo, am now...
Listen, I might be a bit
tangled in my own web now
the happiest I could possibly be!
But once you unravel the mystery,
you'll see pure lo-love